{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622520","name":"Comerica Park- Pitchers Pub","address":"2100 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Detroit Sportservice, Inc. ","licenseNumber":"kg52217","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.04880,42.33918","geojson":{"id":"51622520","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.04879849,42.339180497]},"properties":{"name":"Comerica Park- Pitchers Pub","owner":"Detroit Sportservice, Inc. ","address":"2100 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"kg52217","establishmentid":"51622520","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3475","name":"Chelis Chili Bar","address":"47 E Adams Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2048","name":"Elwood Bar & Grill","address":"300 E Adams","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"355","name":"Detroit Athletic Club","address":"241 Madison Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1265","name":"Central Methodist Church","address":"23 E Adams","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"322","name":"Twentieth Century Club, (Gem Theatre)","address":"333 Madison","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2637","name":"The Fillmore Detroit (State Bar/Theatre)","address":"2101-2115 Woodward Ste 971","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"1680","name":"Michigan Opera Theater","address":"1526 Broadway St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5189","name":"Dilla's Delight's LLC","address":"242 John R","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3706","name":"Angelina Italian Bistro","address":"1565 Broadway","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4694","name":"Madison Building ","address":"1555 Broadway","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5152","name":"Ashe Supply Co.","address":"1555 Broadway St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5132","name":"Vertical Detroit","address":"1538 Centre St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"296","name":"Da Edoardo Foxtown Grille","address":"2203 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5248","name":"234 Winder St. Inn Community Center","address":"2458 Brush St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4262","name":"Ford Field- Bar Portables","address":"2000 Brush St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4884","name":"Ford Field- Detroit Lions Tunnel Club","address":"2000 Brush St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4260","name":"Ford Field- Employee Lounge","address":"2000 Brush St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622506","name":"Ford Field- South Club (Hall of Legends)","address":"2000 Brush St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622504","name":"Ford Field- Terrace Club","address":"2000 Brush St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4255","name":"Ford Field- Levy Rest. (Main Kitchen)","address":"2000 Brush St","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"42840","inspectionDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-202.12","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS shall be:    \r\n(A) Used according to:      \r\n(1) LAW and this Code,   \r\n(2) Manufacturer's use directions included in labeling, and, for a pesticide, manufacturer's label instructions that state that use is allowed in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, (P)   \r\n(3) The conditions of certification, if certification is required, for use of the pest control materials, (P) and   \r\n(4) Additional conditions that may be established by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY; and\r\n(B) Applied so that:      \r\n(1) A HAZARD to EMPLOYEES or other PERSONS is not constituted, (P) and   \r\n(2) Contamination including toxic residues due to drip, drain, fog, splash or spray on FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES is prevented, and for a RESTRICTED USE PESTICIDE, this is achieved by: (P)      \r\n(a) Removing the items, (P)   \r\n(b) Covering the items with impermeable covers, (P) or   \r\n(c) Taking other appropriate preventive actions, (P) and   \r\n(d) Cleaning and SANITIZING EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS after the application. (P)  \r\n(C) A RESTRICTED USE PESTICIDE shall be applied only by an applicator certified as defined in 7 USC 136 Definitions, (e) Certified Applicator, of the Federal Insecticide, Fungicide, and Rodenticide Act, or a PERSON under the direct supervision of a certified applicator. (Pf)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not used according to manufacturer's label instructions","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Pest Control Device","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Use according to manufacturer label directions."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"At the COLD HOLDING TEMPERATURES","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."},{"violationCode":"4-603.16","violationDescription":"Washed UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT shall be rinsed so that abrasives are removed and cleaning chemicals are removed or diluted through the use of water or a detergent-SANITIZER solution by APPROVED procedures.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Washed equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not rinsed","subProblem":"After washing and before sanitizing","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide distinct clear water rinse after washing and before sanitizing."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"38735","inspectionDate":"2017-05-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Ice holding bin","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the AIR GAP","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-07-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"At the COLD HOLDING TEMPERATURES","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\r\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\r\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\r\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Menu advisories","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MENU(S)","subLocation":"At the Consumer Advisory","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-07-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Chemical container","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"At the Hand washing signage","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"2-401.11","violationDescription":"(A)    An EMPLOYEE shall eat, drink, or use any form of tobacco only in designated areas where the contamination of exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES; or other items needing protection can not result.\r\n(B)     A FOOD EMPLOYEE may drink from a closed BEVERAGE container if the container is handled to prevent contamination of:\r\n         (1)     The EMPLOYEE'S hands;\r\n         (2)     The container; and\r\n         (3)     Exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Beverage container","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored improperly","subProblem":"With clean equipment/utensils/linens","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Employee beverages","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on face","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"At the Hair Restraints/Covering","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide beard net."},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Ice bin","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"42211","inspectionDate":"2017-04-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622520"}}